

Profile

Passionate front-end developer with 3+ years of work experience. Worked on large-scale projects, for example, an app for traveling, CMS, Crypto HD wallet, etc. Skilled in Vue.js, Nuxt.js, HTML, CSS/SASS/PostCSS, JavaScript, TypeScript, Bootstrap, Quasar, Rest API, Cypress, Figma.

Employment History

Front-end developer, Gauss Development, Osijek

OCTOBER 2018 - SEPTEMBER 2020

Front-end developer, Barrage, Osijek

SEPTEMBER 2020 - PRESENT

Education

Computer technician, Technical School Nikola Tesla, Vukovar

SEPTEMBER 2014 - MAY 2018

Publication

Top 8 SASS mixins to speed up your frontend development process

APRIL 2021

One of the challenges in a developer's life is speeding up and automating the development process while keeping high-quality standards. A great solution for front-end developers using SASS is its mixin capability.

See publication

Details

Vukovar, 32010 Croatia <u>thealex991@gmail.com</u>

Links

Portfolio

LinkedIn

Skills

Vue.js

Nuxt.js

HTML5

CSS3/SASS/PostCSS

JavaScript

TypeScript

Rest API

Git

Cypress

Bootstrap

Quasar

Figma